Guide to the James Ferlo Papers, 1963-2015 AIS.1998.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pittsburgh City Council, 1963-2010; 1987-2002; I.
  - Alphabetical Subject Files, 1976-2003; 1987-2001; 1.
    - Schenley Manor Drive, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Scott Electric, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Scullin Development, 1999-2002 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Section 8 Housing, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Seldom Seen, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Sellers- Carnahan House, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Service Corps of Retired Executives, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - SPRPC, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Shade Tree Commission, 1994-1998 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Shadyside Parking Garage, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Sharp's Bar, 1988-1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Shaw- Proclamations, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Shaw- Proclamations, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Shaw- Proclamations, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Sheraden Community Council, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Sheridan Youth Center, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Shop 'n' Save, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Sidewalk Notices, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Sideyard, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Signs, 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Silent Complaint, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Single Point of Contact, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Sister Cities Designation, 1990-2000 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Sixty-Second Street City Property, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Skate Park and Walking Loop, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Slum Landlords, 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Small Businesses, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Small Games of Chance, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Snow Job, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Soccer, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Soccer Fields, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Social Investing, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Soldano, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Sol Gross, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Sony File and Pittsburgh Digital Greenhouse, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - South Africa, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - South Side Skating Rink, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - South Side 21st. Street Vacation, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Spiniello Construction, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Spodobalski, Joe, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Southwestern Pa. Regional Planning Commission, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Spray Paint Ordinance, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Squirrel Hill Giant Eagle, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Stadium Development, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Stanton Avenue and Chislett Street Hillside, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Station Square, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - State of World Forum, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Steel Industry Heritage Project, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Steel Plates, 1994-1998 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Steel Valley Authority, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Stooges, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Stop Signs, 1982-1999 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Stop the Train, 1982-1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Strategy 21, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Street Face, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Street Paving, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stumpf's Market, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Sufak, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Sufrin, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Subpoena Fees, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Sullivan Field, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Summer Food Program, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Summer Youth Jobs, 1992-2000 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - SNAC, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Sunshine Act, 1993-1999 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Super Playground, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Sweatshop, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Swimming Pools, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Swimming Pool Fees, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Taxing Body Project, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Tax Rates, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Tax Increment Financing, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Tax Refunds, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Tax Refund Legislation, 1991-1994 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Telephone Message Forms, undated (Box 22, Folder 24-25)
    - Thank Yous, 1994-1997 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Thomas Merton Center, 1990-2001 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Thomas Nominations, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Three Rivers Art Festival, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Three Rivers Center for Independent Living, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Tickets/Citations, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Tourism, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Tow Zones, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Towing, 1991-1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Town Hall Meeting Information, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Toy Lending Library, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Traffic Conditions: Main and BUtler Streets, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Trails, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Transmission Project, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer's Sale Information, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Tree Commission, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tree Fund, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Tri-State Conference on Steel General, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - TriWard Baseball, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Truancy Abatement Center, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Trudeau, Julie, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Tuition Reimbursement, 1990-2001 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Twin Trees, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Union Address, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Union- Allegheny Prison Employees, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Union Baptist, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Union (AFL-CIO-CLC)- United Steel Workers of America, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Union- District 65- Iron City Legal Assistance Workers, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Union- Firefighters, 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Union - Foremen, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Union- Fraternal Order of Police, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Unions- General, 1988-1993 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Union- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Union- Local #3- International Allliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Union - 1199, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Union- International Operating Engerineers, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Union- Paramedics, 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Union Printers, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Union Project, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - United Mine Workers, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - United Citizens Against Narcotics, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - United Way, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - University of Pittsburgh Men's Study, 1987-1991 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - University of Pittsburgh Medical Center, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - University of Pittsburgh Medical Center Pharmacy Network, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Urban Forests, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Urban Homesteading Program, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Urban League- General, 1987-1991 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - URA, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - URA/Planning Department Merger, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Ursuline Center, 1988-1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ursuline Expansion, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Utilities, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Vacant Lots, 1998-2002 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Vacant Property Review Commission, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - VASCAR, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Vending, circa 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Vendors, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Vendor Legislation, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Verifications, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Veterans Administration, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Veteran's Day Parade, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Veteran's Day Parade Permit, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1988-1998 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Veterans Natoli, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Veteran Police Association, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Veterinarian- City, 1984-1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Victoria Hall, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Video Poker Machines, 1988-1993 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Villa de Marillac Nursing Home, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Villanova Property Proposal, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Villanova Road, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Vintage, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Vintage Grand Prix, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Virus- Computer Purge Directions, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Volpe Jr., Charles, circa 1987 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Voter's Voice, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Warehouse Space, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - W & W Demolition, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Wage Tax, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Walkowski, Ed, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Washington Marina, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Water Authority Transfer, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Water and Sewer, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Waterworks, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Wayfinder's, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Weatherization Information, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Wecht, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Weed and Seed, 1995-1999 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - WE-HAV, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Welfare Lien, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - West End Elliot Overlook, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Western Pennsylvania Campaign for Comprehensive Test Ban, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Western Pennsylvania Conservancy, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - West Penn Hospital Parking Lot, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Wetlands, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Whole Foods, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Wholey's, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Wiggins Street, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Wiles, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Witness Protection, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Women's Enterprise Center, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Working Group on Community Development, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Working Together, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - World Trade Center, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - WQEX Sale, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - WM, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - WWII Memorial, circa 2000 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Yazoo, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - YMCA, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Young Democrats, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Youth Initiatives, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Youth Policy, 1993-2001 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Zambelli, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Zone 2- Valenta, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Zone Council, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Zoning Board, 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Zoning Board Arguments, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Zoning Changes, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Zoning Code, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Zoning Code Rewrite, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Zoning Code Review Committee, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Zoning District Map, 1986-1990 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Zoning Study, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Zoning Study, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - City Council, 1978-2001; 1987-2000; 2.
    The City Council subseries contains materials related to issues specific to Pittsburgh and its city council, in particular about the City Council building, phones, fleet, districts, job openings, contacts, funds, in addition to personal materials such as Ferlo's resume, taxes, and statements.
    - Beeper/Pager and Cell Phone, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - CBO Contacts, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cellular Phone/Chauffer, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - City Bond Debt, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - City County Building- Asbestos Testing, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - City County Building- 6th Floor Lease Documents, 1978-1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - City County Building Security, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - City County Services, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - City Court, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - City Court Statements, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - City Court- Tow Pound, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - City Fleet Budget, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - City Lawsuits, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - City Leases, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - City Paramedics, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - City Trash Receptacle, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - City Vehicles, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - City Development Report, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - City Net, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - City Operating Support, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - City Owned Vehicles Rules and Regulations, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - City of Pittsburgh Emergency Operations Plan, circa 1994 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - City Source, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Community Guide to City Services, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Congressional Districts, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Council Chambers Restoration, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Council Committees, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Council District 7 Directory, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Council Money, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Council Photos, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - City Council- Presentation, 1988 July 14 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Council- Presidency Lawsuit, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 32-34)
    - Council- Presidency Lawsuit- Opinion and Court Order, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Council Vacancy- Staff Issues, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Council- Work Order Forms, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - County Council, circa 2000 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - County Jail Issues, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Department Heads/City Directors, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Directories, undated (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Elected Municipal Offices, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Employees Awards, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Employee Citizenship, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Employees-City, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Employee Ownership Handbook, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Employee Subpoena, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Ferlo Biography, circa 1990 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Ferlo- Disclosure Statements, 1992-1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Ferlo- Encumbrances, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Ferlo-Health Benefits, circa 1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Ferlo- Mail List, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Ferlo-Petitions, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Ferlo-Resume, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Ferlo- Taxes/Finances, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Ferlo-Statements, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Filing, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - General Information Booklets, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Job Openings, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Layoffs, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Media Contacts, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Media File, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Municipal Courts, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Pension Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Pension Legislation, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Pension Trust Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Personnel, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Personnel Appeal, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Personnel Problems, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Phone Bills, 1994-1997 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Phone System, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Practical Guide for Municipalities, circa 1995 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Reappropriation of Districts, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Report to Council, Effect of Dual Land Tax, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Resumes, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Rolodex, undated (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - State-City Council Budgets, 1987-1990 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - URA Salaries, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - City Departments, 1983-2002; 1988-2001; 3.
    The City Departments subseries contains materials related to Pittsburgh city departments, including the Bureau of Building Inspection, the City Clerk, Engineering and Construction, Environmental Services, Finances, General Services, Housing, Historic Review Commission, Law, Mayor's Office, Courts, Planning Commission, Parks and Recreation, Public Safety (Fire, Police, and EMS), Public Works, Water, and Zoning.
    - Bureau of Building Inspection, 1998-2002 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Bureau of Building Inspection- Condemnation, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of Fire, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - BCR-1 (Board of Code Review), 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - CCK-1 City Clerk, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - CCL-1 City Council- General, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - CCL-3 City Council Budget, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - CCL-3-2 City Council Budget, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - CHR-1 Commission on Human Relations, 1992-2000 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Department of Aging, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Department of Community Affairs, Applications, 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Department of Public Safety, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Department of Public Works, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - District Offices, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - EC-1-1 Engineering and Construction- General- Reports, 1990-2000 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - EC-2 Engineering and Construction-Anotible Traffic Signal, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - EC-3 Engineering and Construction- Bridge Inspection, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - EC-4 Engineering and Construction- Ornamental Fencing, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - EC-5 Engineering and Construction- McArdle Roadway, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Engineering and Construction-Reports, 1998-2001 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - ES-2-1 Environmental Services- Spay and Neuter Program, circa 1990 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - ES-3 Environmental Services- Garbage, 1988-1992 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - ES-4 Environmental Services- Rodent Control, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - FI-1 Finance- General, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - FI-2 Finance- Workers Compensation, 1988-1992 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - FI-3 Finance- City Depositories, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - FI-4 Finance- Pension File, 1991-2000 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - FI-5-1 Finance-Tax-Discount Period, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - FI-5-2 Finance- Taxes and Amendments, 1988-1991 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - FI-7 Finance- Three Taxing Bodies, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - FI-8 Finance- Municipal Bond Information, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - FI-9 Finance-Civic Arena, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Finance- Evaluation of Financial Institutions Regarding Repository Status, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - GS-1 General Services, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - GS-1-1 General Services- Annual Contract, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - GS-1-7 General Services- Bidding Procedures, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - GS-2 General Services- Gas Card Program, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - GS-2 General Services- Gas Card, 1988-1992 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - GS-3, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - GS-4 General Services- Public Safety Building, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - GS-5 General Services- Mail Room, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - GS-7-1 Pepsi-Cola/ Vending Machine, 1990-1993 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - GS-8, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - GS-8 MBE Court Ruling, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - HRC (Historic Review Commission)- Engine House #1, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - HRC-1 Historic Review Commission-General, 1989-1992 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - HRC-2 Historic Review Commission Ordinance, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - HRC 2-2 Historic Review Commission Supreme Court Decision, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - HRC-3-1 Historic Review Commissions- Guidelines- Exterior Security Device, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - HCR-4-1 Historic Review Commission- Proposals- Shadyside, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - HRC-4-4 Historic Review Commission- Proposal- St. Peter's, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - HRC-4-6, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - HRC-4-7 311 Lowenhill, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - HRC-5 State Initiatives, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Housing Authority, 1999-2001 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Housing Court, 1994-2001 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - LA-1 Law- General, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - LA-2 Law Department- Claims, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - LA-3 Mintwood St., 1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - LA-4, 1988-1992 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Mayor's Office- Commissions, Committees, and Boards, 1989-1991 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Mayor's Office- General, 1990-1992 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Mayor's Office- Task Force, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Mayor's Office- Vetos, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Municipal Courts, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - PC-2-1 Planning Commission- Meetings/Agendas, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - PC-2-2 Planning Commission- Meetings and Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - PCS-1 Personnel and Civil Service Commission- General, 1993-2001 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - PCS-2 Personnel and Civil Service Commission- Single Point of Contact Program, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - PCS-3 Personnel and Civil Service Commission- Summer Jobs, 1990-1992 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - PCS-4 Personnel and Civil Service Commission- Neighborhood Employment Project, 1990-1992 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - PCS-5 Personnel and Civil Service Commission, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - PCS-6 Personnel and Civil Service Commission, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Personnel's Pittsburgh Partnership, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - City Planning 1990 Census Report #3 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - PL-1 Planning Department General, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - PL-2-1 Planning Department Programs and Residential Parking Sticker Program, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - PL-2-2 Planning Department, 1991-1994 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - PL-3-2 Planning Department Studies/ Housing Policy, 1988-1991 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - PL-3-3 Planning Department Studies / Oakland Traffic Studies, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - PL-3-4 Planning Department, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - PL-3-5 Planning Department, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - PL-4-1 Planning Department Projects/ Medical Society, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - PL-4-2 Planning Department, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - PL-4-2 Planning Department, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - PL-4-3 Planning Department, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - PL-4-5 Planning Department Projects- Down by the Riverside, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - PL-4-6 Planning Department Projects / Waterworks Mall Theatre, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - PL-4-7 Planning Department Projects/ PAGIS System, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - PL-4-9 Planning Department / Ellsworth Avenue Bridge, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - PL-5 Planning Department, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Planning Department- Zoning, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - PR-1 Parks and Recreation, 1989-1997 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - PR-3 Golf Course, 1988-1992 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - PR 5-1 Parks and Recreation- Special Projects and Senior Center Programs, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - PR-6 Parks and Recreation- Parks Maintenance, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - PR-6-1 Parks and Recreation- Veterans Monument, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - PR-6-2 Parks and Recreation, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - PS-1- Public Safety- General, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - PS-2- Public Safety- 911, 1989-2001 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - PS-3- Public Safety- Office of Professional Responsibility, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - PS-5 Public Safety- City Photo Lab/Audio/Video Section, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - PS/BBI-1 Bureau of Building Inspection- General, 1991-2001 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - PS/BBI-5 Permit Application, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - PS/EMS-1 Emergency Medical Services General, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - PS/F-1 Bureau of Fire- General, 1988-2001 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - PS/F-1 Bureau of Fire, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - PS/F-2 Bureau of Fire- Pierce Tillers, 1986-1992 (Box 30, Folder 27-28)
    - PS/F-3 Fire NFPA 704, 1985-1988 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - PS/F-4 Fire Truck, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Ps/F-5 Fire Study, 1983-1990 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - PS/P-1 Bureau of Police, 1991-2000 (Box 30, Folder 32)